[
    {
        "front": "みます |",
        "back": "check, take a look at",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "さがします | ",
        "back": "look for, search",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "おくれます || \n[じかんに～]",
        "back": "be late [for an appointment, etc.]",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "まに　あいます | \n[じかんに～]",
        "back": "be in time [for an appointment, etc.]",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "やります |",
        "back": "do ",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ひろいます | ",
        "back": "pickup",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "れんらくします |||",
        "back": "contact, get in touch with",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "きぶんが　いい*",
        "back": "feel well",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "きぶんが　わるい",
        "back": "feel ill",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "うんどうかい",
        "back": "athletic meeting, sports day",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ばんおどり",
        "back": "Bon Festival dance",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "フリーマーケット",
        "back": "flea market",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ばしょ",
        "back": "place ",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ボランティア",
        "back": "volunteer",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "さいふ",
        "back": "wallet, purse",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ごみ",
        "back": "garbage, rubbish, dust",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "こっかいぎじどう",
        "back": "the Diet Building",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "へいじつ",
        "back": "weekday",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "～べん",
        "back": "~dialect",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "こんど",
        "back": "next time, another time",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ずいぶん",
        "back": "very, pretty",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょくせつ",
        "back": "directly",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "いつでも",
        "back": "any time",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "どこでも*",
        "back": "anywhere",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "だれでも*",
        "back": "anybody",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "なんでも*",
        "back": "anything",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "こんな　～*",
        "back": "~like this",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "そんな　～",
        "back": "~like that (near the listener)",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "あんな　～*",
        "back": "~like that (far grom both the speaker and the listener)",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "※エドやストア",
        "back": "fictitious store",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "かたづきます |",
        "back": "[boxes] be put in order, tidy up",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "だします |",
        "back": "put out [the rubbish]",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "もえる　ごみ",
        "back": "burnable rubbish",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "おきば",
        "back": "place where something is put",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "よこ",
        "back": "side",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "びん",
        "back": "bottle",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "かん",
        "back": "can",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "ガス",
        "back": "gas",
        "chapter": 26
    },
    {
        "front": "～かいしゃ",
        "back": "~company",
        "chapter": 26
    }
]